http://www.smithfuneralchapels.com/runtime.php?SiteId=240758&NavigatorId=1063902&op=privacy

Search
Use the form above to find your loved one. You can search using the name of your loved one, or any family name for current or past services entrusted to our firm.
Click here to view all obituaries
Search Obituaries
Immediate Need
We are here to help you. If you have need of our services, please call us, day or night, at:
406-245-6427
To better prepare yourself, we have provided you with some helpful information regarding the immediate need process.
Contact Us / Location
Smith Downtown Funeral Chapel
Smith Downtown Funeral Chapel
925 S 27th Street
BILLINGS, MT 59101
Phone: 406-245-6427
Fax: 406-259-3558
Email: info@smithfuneralchapels.com
Home
Obituaries
Why Come to Us?
Our Difference
Why We're Different
What Makes Us Unique?
Our Story
Our Facilities
Contact Us
Comments & Suggestions
More
Our Services
Creating a Legacy of Memories
Steps in Planning a Funeral or Memorial Service
The First Decision: Burial or Cremation?
What to Know When Choosing Burial
When Cremation is Preferred
Funeral Merchandise
Caskets
Cremation Urns
Burial Vaults
Cremation Vaults
Floral Tributes
When You Meet with the Funeral Home
The First Decision: Burial or Cremation?
Selecting Funeral Products
The Details of Funeral Planning
What to Expect after the Funeral
Immediate Need
A Death has Occurred
Are You the Responsible Family Member?
Online At-Need Funeral Planning
Funeral Pre-Planning
About Funeral Pre-Planning
Benefits of Pre-Planning
Building a Legacy of Memories
Organ & Tissue Donation
Pre-Planning Checklist
Pre-Plan Online
More
Need Assistance?
Contact Us
Grief & Healing
Understanding Grief
The Nature and Purpose of Grief
The Experience of Grieving
Seeking Guidance: Grief Counseling
The Grief Process
Helping Yourself Heal
Coming to Terms with Unexpected Death
Need Assistance?
Contact Us
Help & Guidance
The Moments Before & After Death
Organ & Tissue Donation
Who You Should Call First
How to Tell Family Members
Preparing for the Funeral Service
Writing Down a Life: Crafting the Obituary
Writing and Delivering a Eulogy
Social Expectations: a Primer on Funeral Etiquette
Frequently-Asked-Questions
Facing the Legalities
Gathering the Important Documents
Will I Need a Lawyer?
Death Certificates
Notifying Creditors and Government Agencies
Need Assistance?
Contact Us
Flowers
Order Flowers
Ordering flowers from our site ensures that your order will reach us or the family in a timely manner, and your gesture of support will remain acknowledged in the Book of Memories for future generations. We only work with local florists so we can maintain the sense of urgency and quality of your selections. We thank you for helping to support the family during their time of need, and will fondly remember your kind gesture.
Click Here
Immediate Need
If you have immediate need of our services, we're available for you 24 hours a day.
Order Flowers
Offer a gift of comfort and beauty to a family suffering from loss.
Obituaries & Tributes
It is not always possible to pay respects in person, so we hope that this small token will help.
Pre-Arrangement
A gift to your family, sparing them hard decisions at an emotional time.
Privacy Policy
Smith Downtown Funeral Chapel Privacy Policy
At Smith Downtown Funeral Chapel, we understand that the
privacy of our visitors and the knowledge of our use of information collected
from each visitor is important in our activities. Please feel free to read our
privacy policy and we encourage you to contact our firm about any of the
information located below if you need further assistance.
Contact Information:
If you feel that there is a need to contact
our firm, please use one of the following methods:
Mail:
Smith Downtown Funeral Chapel925 S 27th StreetBILLINGS, MT, USA59101
Phone:
406-245-6427
Email
Address:info@smithfuneralchapels.com
Your IP Address
We collect the IP Address and Domain Name
that is used when surfing our web site. We use this information for Site Traffic
Statistics and analysis. We also receive
your IP Address when you complete a search or purchase on our site in order to help our firm
better recognize what is being searched by our visitors. All IP Addresses and
Domain Names are kept with the utmost confidentiality.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is used by Smith Downtown Funeral Chapel only when
there is persistent data that is required to use the Web Site, ie.
Administration Mode, and when an E-Commerce order form is being completed. For
general viewing of pages, there is no use of cookies.
When a user wishes to purchase product(s)
they will be asked to complete an online form.
When a user completes a section of the form and clicks on the "Next" button, not
only does the form progress to the Next page but a cookie is created on the
visitor's computer with the information that they just completed. The purpose of
the shopping basket cookie is to remember your information so that if you leave
or get disconnected and come back to the order form our server will be able to
complete the sections of the order form for you including product
selected.
E-Commerce Module
To ensure that all data remains
private and secure, we exclusively use secure network
connections. These secure network connections are the only way that
credit card and other personal information is handled. Any and all
sensitive authorization data, including but not limited to credit card
information is never stored by Smith Downtown Funeral Chapel, any employee therein or
FrontRunner Professional. All payment details are securely transmitted
by third party processors on secure networks connections. If you have
any questions please
contact accountingdept@frontrunner360.com.
Questions & Comments
If you have questions, comments or concerns
with either the way we use the information that is collected from your web
browser or our privacy policy, please feel free to contact our firm.
Obituaries
Current Services
Past Services
Why Come to Us?
Our Difference
Our Services
Funeral Merchandise
Obituaries & Commemorations
Funeral Planning
What to Expect
Immediate Need
Funeral Pre-Planning
Need Assistance?
Grief & Healing
Understanding Grief
The Grief Process
Need Assistance?
Help & Guidance
The Moments Before & After Death
Preparing for the Funeral Service
Facing the Legalities
Need Assistance?
Flowers
Order Flowers
Proudly Serving the
Communities of Billings, Laurel, Columbus/Absarokee, Red Lodge, Joliet, Bridger, Belfry. Huntley, Worden, Shepherd, Ballantine, Broadview/Lavina and surrounding areas
406-245-6427
Smith Downtown Funeral Chapel
925 S 27th Street
BILLINGS,
315 East 3rd St.
Laurel,
Billings,
Red Lodge,
